so now that we have seen how to access
the btb let's do a quiz let's say we
have a btb with 1,24 entries note that
these entries would be numers 0 through
1223 let's say that this particular
architecture uses fix size four byte
instructions that have to be word
aligned which means an instruction needs
to begin at a divisible by four address
so an instruction can be at address 0 4
8 Etc but it cannot be at addresses
something like three or five or 17 and
let's say that the program counter is a
32-bit register meaning that this
particular processor uses 32-bit
instruction addresses the question for
you is which btb entry again they are
numbered from 0 to 1023 should be used
for PC whose address is hex 000000 a b0
c right your answer here again the
answer should be between 0 and 1,23